{
  "leaderCards": [
      {
      "effectType": "DISCOUNT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-49.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-49.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "YELLOW", "ANY", "1"], ["FLAG","GREEN", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 2,
      "resource": "SERVANT"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "DISCOUNT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-50.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-50.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "BLUE", "ANY", "1"], ["FLAG", "PURPLE", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 2,
      "resource": "SHIELD"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "DISCOUNT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-51.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-51.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "GREEN", "ANY", "1"], ["FLAG", "BLUE", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 2,
      "resource": "STONE"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "DISCOUNT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-52.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-52.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "YELLOW", "ANY", "1"], ["FLAG", "PURPLE", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 2,
      "resource": "COIN"
    },







      {
      "effectType": "EXTRA_DEPOT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-53.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-53.pdf",
      "cost": [["RESOURCE", "COIN", "5"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 3,
      "resource": "STONE"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "EXTRA_DEPOT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-54.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-54.pdf",
      "cost": [["RESOURCE", "STONE", "5"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 3,
      "resource": "SERVANT"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "EXTRA_DEPOT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-55.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-55.pdf",
      "cost": [["RESOURCE", "SERVANT", "5"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 3,
      "resource": "SHIELD"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "EXTRA_DEPOT",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-56.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-56.pdf",
      "cost": [["RESOURCE", "SHIELD", "5"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 3,
      "resource": "COIN"
    },






    { 
      "effectType": "WHITE_MARBLE",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-57.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-57.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "YELLOW", "ANY", "2"], ["FLAG","BLUE", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 5,
      "marble": "PURPLE"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "WHITE_MARBLE",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-58.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-58.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "GREEN", "ANY", "2"], ["FLAG","PURPLE", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 5,
      "marble": "BLUE"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "WHITE_MARBLE",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-59.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-59.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "BLUE", "ANY", "2"], ["FLAG","YELLOW", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 5,
      "marble": "GREY"
    },
    {
      "effectType": "WHITE_MARBLE",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-60.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-60.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "PURPLE", "ANY", "2"], ["FLAG","GREEN", "ANY", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 5,
      "marble": "YELLOW"
    },





    { 
      "effectType": "PRODUCTION",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-61.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-61.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "YELLOW", "TWO", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 4,
      "productionCost":[["RESOURCE","SHIELD", 1]],
      "productionOutput":[["RESOURCE", "ANY", 1], ["FAITH", 1]]
    },
    {
      "effectType": "PRODUCTION",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-62.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-62.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "BLUE", "TWO", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 4,
      "productionCost":[["RESOURCE","SERVANT", 1]],
      "productionOutput":[["RESOURCE", "ANY", 1], ["FAITH", 1]]
    },
    {
      "effectType": "PRODUCTION",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-63.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-63.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "PURPLE", "TWO", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 4,
      "productionCost":[["RESOURCE","STONE", 1]],
      "productionOutput":[["RESOURCE", "ANY", 1], ["FAITH", 1]]
    },
    {
      "effectType": "PRODUCTION",
      "imageFront" : "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/front/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_FRONT_3mmBleed_1-64.pdf",
      "imageBack": "/img/Cards/LeaderCards/back/Masters of Renaissance_Cards_BACK_3mmBleed_1-64.pdf",
      "cost": [["FLAG", "GREEN", "TWO", "1"]], 
      "victoryPoints": 4,
      "productionCost":[["RESOURCE","COIN", 1]],
      "productionOutput":[["RESOURCE", "ANY", 1], ["FAITH", 1]]
    } 

  ]
}